<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Cinema Wiki</string>
    <string name="overview_movie1">An American teenager named Sean Boswell is a loner in school, however he challenges his rival for an illegal street racing, and he totals his car in the end of the race. To avoid time in prison he is sent to Tokyo to live with his father who is in the military. As soon as he arrives he discovers a new, fun but dangerous way of street racing in the underworld of the streets of Tokyo, Japan.</string>
    <string name="overview_movie2">84 years later, a 100 year-old woman named Rose DeWitt Bukater tells the story to her granddaughter Lizzy Calvert, Brock Lovett, Lewis Bodine, Bobby Buell and Anatoly Mikailavich on the Keldysh about her life set in April 10th 1912, on a ship called Titanic when young Rose boards the departing ship with the upper-class passengers and her mother, Ruth DeWitt Bukater, and her fiancé, Caledon Hockley. Meanwhile, a drifter and artist named Jack Dawson and his best friend Fabrizio De Rossi win third-class tickets to the ship in a game. And she explains the whole story from departure until the death of Titanic on its first and last voyage April 15th, 1912 at 2:20 in the morning.</string>
    <string name="overview_movie3">May/June 1940. Four hundred thousand British and French soldiers are hole up in the French port town of Dunkirk. The only way out is via sea, and the Germans have air superiority, bombing the British soldiers and ships without much opposition. The situation looks dire and, in desperation, Britain sends civilian boats in addition to its hard-pressed Navy to try to evacuate the beleaguered forces. This is that story, seen through the eyes of a soldier amongst those trapped forces, two Royal Air Force fighter pilots, and a group of civilians on their boat, part of the evacuation fleet.</string>
    <string name="overview_movie4">14 years after their budding romance in high-school, Rangga and Cinta reunite in Yogyakarta to have their closure after Rangga had left Cinta with no explanation years prior.</string>
    <string name="overview_movie5">Milea (Vanesha Prescilla) met with Dilan (Iqbaal Ramadhan) at a high school in Bandung in 1990, when Milea moved from Jakarta to Bandung. An unusual introduction brings Milea to know the uniqueness of Dilan, smart, kind, romantic. The way Dilan approaches Milea is not the same as other male friends, even Beni (Brandon Salim), Milea boyfriend in Jakarta. The journey of their relationship is not always smooth. Beni, Anhar (Giulio Perangkan), Kang Adi (Refal Hadi) color the journey. Dilan makes Milea believe that she can arrive at the destination safely.</string>
    <string name="overview_movie6">Dara (Zara JKT48) and Bima (Angga Yunanda) violated the boundary without knowing the consequences. They try to take responsibility for their choices. They think they are ready to become adults to face all the consequences. Their innocence is immediately tested when families who really loved them knew, then forced into their chosen journey.</string>
    <string name="overview_movie7">In Jakarta, Indonesia, Lieutenant Wahyu organizes the invasion of an apartment building that is the safe house of the powerful and cruel drug lord Tama and his gang. The SWAT team breaks in the building but one lookout sees and warns the gangsters and the police force is trapped on the seventh floor. They learn that Lt. Wahyu has not informed his superiors about the operation. Now the police officers have to fight with limited ammunition against the armed and dangerous gangsters.</string>
    <string name="overview_movie8">Mr. Bean enters a church raffle and wins a vacation trip to France as well as a camcorder. After boarding a Eurostar train and arriving in Paris, the French language proves a barrier for Bean, as he struggles to get across the city to catch a train to the south of France from the Gare de Lyon. Taking time to order a meal, he finds the consumption of a seafood platter to be a challenge. Just before catching his train, he asks Emil, a Russian film director on his way to be a judge at the Cannes Film festival to use his camcorder to record his boarding, but accidentally causes Emil being left behind at the station.</string>
    <string name="overview_movie9">With the untimely death of his beloved wife still bitter in his mouth, John Wick, the expert former assassin, receives one final gift from her--a precious keepsake to help John find a new meaning in life now that she is gone. But when the arrogant Russian mob prince, Iosef Tarasov, and his men pay Wick a rather unwelcome visit to rob him of his prized 1969 Mustang and his wife present, the legendary hitman will be forced to unearth his meticulously concealed identity. Blind with revenge, John will immediately unleash a carefully orchestrated maelstrom of destruction against the sophisticated kingpin, Viggo Tarasov, and his family, who are fully aware of his lethal capacity. Now, only blood can quench the boogeyman thirst for retribution.</string>
    <string name="overview_movie10">Rancho is an engineering student. His two friends. Farhan and Raju, Rancho sees the world in a different way. Rancho goes somewhere one day. And his friends find him. When Rancho is found, he has become one of a great scientist in the world.</string>
    <string name="overview_movie11">Cek Toko Sebelah is the tale of a widower father left with a shop to tend. When he has a heart attack, he puts his youngest son Erwin in charge of it. This is an epic movie that tells the story of how the shop gets sold and how Erwin and his brother Yudi devise a plot to win the shop back</string>
    <string name="overview_movie12">After David Kim (John Cho) 16-year-old daughter goes missing, a local investigation is opened and a detective is assigned to the case. But 37 hours later and without a single lead, David decides to search the one place no one has looked yet, where all secrets are kept today: his daughter laptop. In a hyper-modern thriller told via the technology devices we use every day to communicate, David must trace his daughter digital footprints before she disappears forever.</string>
    <string name="overview_movie13">Earth future has been riddled by disasters, famines, and droughts. There is only one way to ensure mankind survival: Interstellar travel. A newly discovered wormhole in the far reaches of our solar system allows a team of astronauts to go where no man has gone before, a planet that may have the right environment to sustain human life.</string>
    <string name="overview_movie14">Chronicles the experiences of a formerly successful banker as a prisoner in the gloomy jailhouse of Shawshank after being found guilty of a crime he did not commit. The film portrays the man unique way of dealing with his new, torturous life; along the way he befriends a number of fellow prisoners, most notably a wise long-term inmate named Red.</string>
    <string name="overview_movie15">The Godfather "Don" Vito Corleone is the head of the Corleone mafia family in New York. He is at the event of his daughter wedding. Michael, Vito youngest son and a decorated WW II Marine is also present at the wedding. Michael seems to be uninterested in being a part of the family business. Vito is a powerful man, and is kind to all those who give him respect but is ruthless against those who do not. But when a powerful and treacherous rival wants to sell drugs and needs the Don influence for the same, Vito refuses to do it. What follows is a clash between Vito fading old values and the new ways which may cause Michael to do the thing he was most reluctant in doing and wage a mob war against all the other mafia families which could tear the Corleone family apart.</string>
</resources>